Julius Gold Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Printed Music (Box 17, Box OV 3)
  - Piano scores by A. Arensky, C. P. E. Bach, J. S. Bach (2 piano), L. van Beethoven, Franz Bendel, Mathilde Bilbro (2 piano), Fr. von Esterhazy, Leopold Godowsky, Halfdan Kjerulf, Aug. Labitzky, Heinrich Lichner, Immanuel Liebich, Dorothy McGrath, Moritz Moszkowski, Ottorino Respighi (2 piano), Joachim Raff, Erno Rapée, James H. Rogers, Robert Schumann, Trygve Torjussen, and Mortimer Wilson [alphabetically by composer; 3 folders] (Box 17)
  - Piano/vocal scores by Buenta Carter, Palmer John Clark, Franco Leoni, Arthur Lee Mancebo, James H. Rogers, Meredith Willson, and Lawrence Zenda (Box 17)
  - Fragments (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 17)